A Guide to the Judy de la Gueronniere collection of William Rockefeller FA404
Rockefeller Archive Center
Judy de la Gueronniere collection of William Rockefeller
1920s-1930s
Rockefeller Archive Center
de la Gueronniere, Judy
FA404
2.48 Cubic Feet 2 standard letter sized boxes and 5 oversized flat boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
As received.
Scope and Contents
Primarily consists of still images.
- 2009:081, 5 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  William Goodsell Rockefeller in court dress – London (removed from frame) Godfrey Stillman Rockefeller in uniform Godfrey Stillman Rockefeller (March 1942) William Goodsell Rockefeller (Blank & Stoller Inc. Studio) Almira Geraldine Goodsell Rockefeller
- 1933-4-5-6, 1933-1936; 1 photo album (Box 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4)
- Florida, Skiing, 1936-1937; 92 35mm color glass slides (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Wyoming I, 1937; 99 35mm color glass slides (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Southwest Sulfur, 1937; 98 35mm color glass slides (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Yosemite II, 1938; 97 35mm color glass slides (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Baby's Kingdom, 1899 May 1; 1 Scrapbook (Box 3)
- Godfrey Stillman Rockefeller, 1 photo album (Box 4)
- GSR Around the World, 1921; 1 Scrapbook/photo album (Box 5)
- 1930-1936, 1 scrapbook/photo album (Box 6)
- Oversized, 12 photographic prints (Box 7)
  From 2009:081 2 halftone prints of William & Almira Geraldine Rockefeller seated William Rockefeller William Goodsell Rockefeller Rockwood Hall Almira Geraldine Goodsell Rockefeller (in court dress London 42484) William Goodsell Rockefeller (same as framed photo- Lafayette's Mezzo Tint) Godfrey Stillman undated 2 prints of Helen Gratz Rockefeller (wife of Godfrey Stillman Rockefeller) (1 from Kajiwaza Studio, 1 unknown studio)
  From 2011:044 Mrs. Stillman and children Stillman Family photo